Hello I'm

# **ROHIT LIKHALA**

## **Graphic Designer & Video Editor**

- mohitlikhala7@gmail.com
- <u>\$\ +91-823988</u>8863
- <u> +91-882468</u>8174
- Jaipur, Rajasthan





# **About Me**

I am a Graphic & Concept Designer based in Jaipur. I have done B.Tech. in Computer Science Engineering with a little work experience in Web Development (mostly in MEAN stack technology). My professional skill set include graphic designing & video/photo editing on Adobe Premiere Pro CC, Adobe Photoshop CS3, Adobe illustrator and Cyberlink PowerDirector 17.

Photography has always been the north star of my life, majorly landscape, wildlife, portraits and macros. Nature's simplicity and people's lives always sparks a irresistible passion in me and I always try to find a missing prospect in all of them.

**Dancing** 

Fitness Enthusiast

Hodophile

# What I do

# **Designing / Editing**

I develop the overall layout and design for advertisements, websites, youtube videos and corporate videos. I use to work with text, images & video clips.

#### **Tools**

Adobe Photoshop CS5, Adobe Premiere Pro CC, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Cyberlink PowerDirector

## **Projects**

- 1. Mental Health App Moodboard
- 2. The Unfiltered Principals
- 3. Sanskriti University Brochure
- 4. Study in India Edudite Magazine
- 5. Jazba Theatre Club Website

## **Technical Knowledge**

Adobe Photoshop CS5	Advanced
Adobe Premiere Pro CC	Intermediate
Cyberlin PowerDirector	Advanced
Adobe Illustrator	Intermediate
Adobe InDesign	Intermediate

#### **Professional Skills**

- Communication
- Team Work
- Creativity
- Team Leader
- Project Management

## Languages

- Hindi
- English
- Punjabi (Conversational)

#### **Education**

#### **Computer Science Engineering**

Poornima Group of Institutions, Jaipur

2016-2020

#### High School

Kendriya Vidyalaya, Churu

2006 - 2016

#### **Certifications**

#### Fundamental of Digital Marketing -

<u>Google</u>

(Use Credentials – W%J CXQ XFY)

Oct - 2020

#### Best IBM Performance Award -

PGI, Jaipur

Sept - 2019

Event Coordinator – 10th

**Intercollegiate Annual Tech-Cult-**

**Sports Fest** 

Sept - 2019

## **Experience**

#### Graphic Designer Padhai Help Pvt. Ltd.

July 2020 - Nov

Role:

- Logo Designing
- Video/Photo Editing
- Animation

#### Graphic Designer Edudite Consultancy Pvt. Ltd.

Dec 2020 – Present

- Digital/Social Media Creative's & Web Banners
- Video/Photo Editing
- Newsletters
- Concept Designing
- Promotional Campaigns for Print & Web

#### Freelance Graphic Designer Get Marketed

Apr 2021 - Present

Role:

- Social Media Posts/Carousels/Web Banners
- Social Media Video/Reels Editing
- Conceptualization of Designs
- Ad & Campaign Management

### **Personal Details**

Date of birth: 07.07.1998

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Single / Unmarried

Nationality: Indian